CHRIS ROSCHI

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+61 448 865 668

chrisroschi53@gmail.com

Adelaide, Australia

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp

Adelaide University | 2020

Bachelor of Business, Sport & Recreation Management

UniSA | 2015-2017

SKILLS

Programming Languages / Libraries:

» HTML/CSS » JavaScript

» ¡Query » React

» Ajax » API's

» Node.js
» Express

» Handlebars » SQL/MySQL

» MongoDB

CMS' / Frameworks:

» Bootstrap » WordPress

» Oncord » Shopify

» Divi

Software:

» PhotoShop » InDesign

» Acrobat Pro » Visual Studio

» Git » Heroku

PROFILE

Currently studying Full Stack Web Development through Adelaide University and working as a Front End Web Developer for a Graphic & Digital Design company. Completed a Bachelor of Business Sport & Recreation Management at the University of South Australia in 2017. Two years of experience with web design & development with a good understanding of both on-site & off-site SEO. Experience with various CMS' including WordPress, Oncord, Shopify and Neto. Knowledge of Visual Studio, GitHub, Heroku, Google Analytics & AdWords, Adobe Software and Google Sheets/Excel.

I have excellent cognitive ability, especially when it comes to new software, which allows me to hastily grasp unfamiliar processes and tasks. I'm a competent worker and proficient when working autonomously or in a group environment.

Participated in team sport for over ten years and have often taken up leadership roles, including captaining the first team at Adelaide University Whites Soccer Club.

EXPERIENCE

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

CREATIVE POD | ADELAIDE, AUSTRALIA | AUG 2020- PRESENT

Teaming up with graphic design professionals to create innovative web, digital and print marketing solutions for a wide variety of businesses and individuals.

- » Converting static wireframe designs into websites using HTML, CSS & JS.
- » Coding fully functioning and clean looking websites from scratch.
- » Working with numerous content management systems including WordPress, Oncord, Shopify & Neto.
- » Managing and updating various eCommerce websites.
- » Working closely with graphic designers to improve overall look and flow of websites.
- » Implementing SEO best practices to improve both onsite & offsite SEO.

TECHNICAL ASSISTANT

MGA INSURANCE BROKERS | ADELAIDE, AUSTRALIA | SEPT 2018 - AUG 2020

Valued member of an operations team that worked closely with the managers of multiple different areas including Marketing, Compliance, Training and IT.

- » Redesigned and built two new public facing websites www.mga.com & www.mga.
- » Managed and updated six different WordPress websites (both public facing and intranets)
- » Worked on improving both on-site & off-site SEO

INTERESTS

Programming, Soccer, Movies & TV, Camping, Podcasts

- » Worked in a team of two to migrate numerous WordPress websites to new host servers
- » Created tenders, brochures, flyers, information packs and other documents using Adobe InDesign
- » Created numerous digital PDF forms using InDesign & Adobe Acrobat Pro

REFERENCES

Haydn Clark Creative Director

Creative Pod haydn@creativepod.com.au +61 407 607 284

JOSH MCDONALD Broking & Technical Coordinator

MGA Insurance Brokers josh.mcdonald@mga.com +61 417 816 799

PAUL GEORGE

Managing Director

MGA Insurance Brokers paul.george@mga.com +61 409 673 002

STEVEN MCINERNEY Marketing Manager

MGA Insurance Brokers steven.mcinerney@mga.com +61 417 816 799